I was sitting on the bus ride back from
Whistler coming up with synonyms for
Union one of which was legion alliance
you almost ate Avengers but that wasn't
right
collaborators and none of them really
spoke to me but I took alliance because
there's a just BC disability alliance is
one of the ways one people that helps
with very specific paperwork in DC and
so I don't want to reuse the same
especially in BC and so disability
Alliance doesn't quite work and so
looking up the synonyms leagues both me
and when I clicked on league not only is
it of course an association or
Federation is the noun the definition
with the noun one of the noun sorry one
of the other nouns some of the other
definitions is a group of a certain
ability and so the disability League in
basically anywhere is thought of as the
bottom lead the one that you basically
need to prove that you're the bottom in
order to be able to participate in we're
not gonna require any proof but us the
people who society does not work for we
don't earn enough money we aren't able
to contribute in our own way we often
can't work at least full time our
accessibility needs are expensive and
looked at as a burden were looked at as
a burden on society and we are anything
but when actually able to contribute in
our own unique ways what we have to
offer not despite our disabilities but
directly because we have those
disabilities is going to unlock a whole
new evolution for Humanity not one we're
all perfect to me getting Gattaca
because there is no perfect we are
perfect already exactly as
we are with our diversity of bodies and
our diversity of minds and our diversity
of emotions
we're already exactly who we're supposed
to be but we're gonna take what society
looks at as the bottom we already don't
give a we already see it judging us
so why convince people who are living
their life for the judgment of society
that they shouldn't when instead we can
just get together people who already
realize they're getting judged and it's
ridiculous
and then with the world's like a
ballista and create a world that works
for us using technology creating the
social media platform designed for
people with disabilities to collaborate
on creating a society in a world and a
life that works for them as an
individual so welcome to the disability
League our new tech cooperative that is
going to focus on those solutions it's
the same first project we're still doing
the hope cafe although now I feel it
needs a different name but League I will
see you tomorrow a better world that's
on its way it's gonna be brought to you
by the physically and mentally diverse
the Douro diverse subscribe